{
    "subject": "resource/Zorro's_Black_Whip",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Linda_Stirling",
    "human_readable": "Linda Stirling stars in Zorro's Black Whip.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8946656584739685,
            "question": "Was Zorro a popular character in film during Linda Stirling's time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8536270260810852,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Zorro's Black Whip?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8288809657096863,
            "question": "Which actor played Zorro in Zorro's Black Whip?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7872090339660645,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Linda Stirling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6042269468307495,
            "question": "Are there any other films starring Linda Stirling that are known for adventure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.53887540102005,
            "question": "What other roles did Linda Stirling play besides action heroines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5225766897201538,
            "question": "Is Linda Stirling known for acting in Western films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5144159197807312,
            "question": "Was Linda Stirling a popular actress during the Golden Age of Hollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43137845396995544,
            "question": "What genre is the film Zorro's Black Whip?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42676758766174316,
            "question": "What is the plot of Zorro's Black Whip?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Linda Stirling stars in Zorro's Black Whip.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3071_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Zorro's Black Whip?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3071_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Linda Stirling a popular actress during the Golden Age of Hollywood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3071_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Linda Stirling known for acting in Western films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3071_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3071_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Linda Stirling starred in the film serial \"Zorro\u2019s Black Whip\" (1944), which directly supports the statement that Linda Stirling stars in Zorro's Black Whip."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}